#### Lara Janecka

738 Keats Way Waterloo Ontario N2T 2Y2 lara.janecka@gmail.com 226-808-1141

The expansion of my skill sets and gaining valued and immediate experience in a broad variety of software development disciplines are my primary goals, and would generate from me my best effort and engagement to further the objectives of my employer.

#### SKILLS SUMMARY

Functional with Java, Python, C, C++, HTML and CSS

Currently learning Ruby, and BASH

Experience with bug tracking software MKS and code respository GitHub

Experience coding in Vim, Eclipse, Netbeans, and Sublime Text

Work experience with Selenium and in house automation tools

Capable in Windows and Linux

#### OTHER USEFUL FACTS

Dual-Citizenship, can work in Canada or USA

#### **SOFT SKILLS**

Excellent problem solving skills; Careful eye for detail particularly for debugging; Outstanding communication and interpersonal skills, highly self-motivated and energetic

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

**Quality Assurance Analyst,** Masstech, Markham, ON, April 2013 – August 2013

- Regression and unit testing, including the release of two builds
- Automation scripting
- Wrote scripts and parsers for use in automation
- Technical writing and documentation of test procedures

**Storefront Operator,** Tim Horton's, Waterloo, ON, October 2009 – November 2012

- Provided customers with excellent and timely service
- Multitasked during busy times
- Trained new employees

#### **EDUCATION**

Candidate for Bachelors of Software Engineering (Co-op Program), University of Waterloo, Waterloo, ON, Sept 2012-present Relevant Courses: Program Principles, Introduction to Methods of Software Engineering, and Introduction to Sequential Programming

**Ontario High School Diploma,** Sir John A. MacDonald Secondary School, Waterloo, ON, June 20

### Mission Pokescape, Computer Science, April. – June. 2012

- Co-Wrote a dungeon crawler based on Pokemon Mystery Dungeon in Java using the Netbeans GUI
- Designed all levels using Tiled
- Coded enemy AI

## Scribbler Robots, Introduction to Methods of Software Engineering, Sept/2012 - Dec/2012

- Led team of six in the development and implementation of a Python program
- Programmed a robot to navigate color-coded paths to retrieve objects
- Wrote proposals and project reports

# Student Launch Initiative, San Antonio, Texas, Jan 2007 – Aug 2007

- Co-wrote proposal to NASA for funding
- Aided in the design and testing of a rocket used to level ozone levels in the lower atmosphere
- Tested rocket at NASA facility in Alabama
- Co-wrote post-launch report

#### **AWARDS**

- President's Scholarship, University of Waterloo, Waterloo, ON, 2012
- Top %4 of Hypatia Math Contest
- Achieved Honor Roll all four years of high school

# **HOBBIES**

Archery, martial arts, music (guitar), and literature